<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 08:43:09 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When choosing Mutiny in Quarkus REST</title>
      <link>/posts/quarkus-munity-uni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 08:43:09 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/quarkus-munity-uni/</guid>
      <description>When choosing Mutiny in Quarkus REST Scenario 1: Simple Synchronous Operation @GET @Produces(MediaType.TEXT_PLAIN) public String greeting() { return &amp;#34;Hello!&amp;#34;; } Use Case: You have a straightforward operation that completes quickly and doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve any asynchronous tasks (database queries, network calls, etc.).&#xA;Why No Uni: In this case, using Uni would introduce unnecessary complexity. You can simply return the result directly as a String.&#xA;Scenario 2: Asynchronous Operation with a Single Result @GET @Produces(MediaType.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Logging for Java 11 HttpClient</title>
      <link>/posts/java-httpclient-loggin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:49:50 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/java-httpclient-loggin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Java&amp;rsquo;s java.net.http.HttpClient (introduced in Java 11) provides a modern and standardized way to perform HTTP requests. Enabling detailed logging for this client offers invaluable insights when troubleshooting network issues, analyzing request/response behavior, and optimizing application performance.&#xA;To enable the log, add this JVM option -Djdk.httpclient.HttpClient.log=errors,requests when staring your application.&#xA;Code example I use this library as a client to call OpenAI API, the library uses httpclient for making http request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Datatype - Strings</title>
      <link>/posts/python-datatype-strings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 05:17:19 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/python-datatype-strings/</guid>
      <description>Strings: The Textual Heart of Python In Python, strings are sequences of characters used to represent text. You can think of them as an ordered collection of letters, numbers, symbols, and spaces. To define a string, you enclose your text within:&#xA;Single quotes, double quotes Python is flexible with strings. You can enclose them in eithers in single quotes &#39; or double quotes &amp;quot;.&#xA;s1 = &amp;#39;Hello world&amp;#39; # Single quotes s2 = &amp;#34;Hello world&amp;#34; # Double quotes The key is to be consistent, but there are times you&amp;rsquo;ll want to include one type of quote within a string enclosed by the other type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two worth living places in Vietnam</title>
      <link>/posts/worth-living-place-vn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:11:53 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/worth-living-place-vn/</guid>
      <description>When considering where to live in Vietnam, it is important to define what makes a place &amp;ldquo;worth living&amp;rdquo;. Nowadays, remote work is more feasible, especially for software programmers like me. So for me, a worth living place is one that is easy to get around, affordable for living, and offers plenty of opportunities to immerse oneself in nature.&#xA;Criteria Walking condition If you love to walk, Vietnam can be challenging place to live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First open-source contribution</title>
      <link>/posts/first-open-source-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 15:11:55 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/first-open-source-contribution/</guid>
      <description>Motivation First contribution to an open-source is the significant milestone in my journey as a software engineer, it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to learn and give back to the community.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m currently working for Gridly, which is a content management and localization system. Gridly has a feature called Connector and it uses Airbyte internally for syncing data from other sources to Gridly.&#xA;Airbyte Gridly connector So, I decided to write Gridly as a source connector to sync data to other destinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start to write</title>
      <link>/posts/start-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 15:11:53 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/start-to-write/</guid>
      <description>I am not proficient in language, including my native Vietnamse, so even after years of learning English, I am still struggling to master it.&#xA;No, the above paragraph is not my orignial one. It&amp;rsquo;s the version from ChatGPT.&#xA;And my second one as well.&#xA;And &amp;hellip;&#xA;But they doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter though, what matters now is that I have decided to start to write a blog.&#xA;And yes, you should probably know why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>/hire-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 19:32:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/hire-me/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I works as a full-time employee for Gridly. I&amp;rsquo;m not available for a new opportunity right now. But for my long-term plan, I would love to have a remote job. In case you have one and want to hire me, please check my Linkedin&amp;rsquo;s profile, and my cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 19:14:51 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Tan Ho, and I&amp;rsquo;m a Senior Java Backend Developer at Gridly based in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. I&amp;rsquo;m also a proud husband and father of two.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
