<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tan Ho</title>
    <link>http://honhattan.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tan Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 08:40:48 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://honhattan.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter Introduction</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-9-flutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 08:40:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-9-flutter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character Encoding</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-7-character-encoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 10:09:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-7-character-encoding/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s character encoding? Words and sentenses are created from characters. Those characters are stored in computers in bytes.
Basically, you can visuallize by assuming all characters are stored in computer using a special code. A character encoding provides a key to unlock the code. It is set of a mappings between bytes in computers and the characters in character set. Without key, the data looks like garbage.
Unicode Unicode assigns unique numbers to characters used all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Five - Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-5-elasticsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 16:41:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-5-elasticsearch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Four - Understanding JSON Web Token(JWT)</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-4-understanding-jwt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 16:40:42 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-4-understanding-jwt/</guid>
      <description>What is JSON Web Token JSON Web Token as known as JWT, is a means of transmitting information between two parties in a compact, verifiable form.
JWT can be signed using a secret (with HMAC algorithm) or a public/private key pair using RSA or ECDSA.
When to use it What is data structrure inside it. In a compact form, a JWT contains three parts, separated by dot ( . ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Go</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-3-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:09:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-3-golang/</guid>
      <description>Go is statically typed, complied programming language designed at Google by Robert Griesemer (V8 engine, Java Hotspt VM), Rob Pike (Unix Team, UTF-8) and Ken Tompson (Unix).
It&amp;rsquo;s similar to C but memory safety, garbage collection, structral typing, and CSP-type concurrency.
 Did the C++ committee really believe that what was wrong with C++ was that it didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough features?
&amp;ndash; Rob Pike &amp;ndash;
Robert: Starting point: C, fix some obvious flaws, remove crud, add a few missing features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Daemon Thread</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-2-java-thread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 17:51:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-2-java-thread/</guid>
      <description>A daemon thread is a thread that is considered doing some tasks in the background like handling requests or various chronjobs that can exits in an application.
Properties  It can not prevent JVM from exiting when all user threads finish their executions. It is an utmost low priority thread.  Methods  public final void setDaemon(boolean on): This method is used to mark the current thread as daemon thread or normal thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask Framework</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-1-flask-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 20:08:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/day-1-flask-framework/</guid>
      <description>Create a new environment for our example.
conda create -n myflask python=3.7.3 flask We create an envionment with flask package and specified python version 3.7.3. If version is not specified, newest version is downloaded.
Below is what the output will look like on my terminal.
(base) tan@tan-pc:~/Workspace/py/my-flask-app$ conda create -n myflask python=3.7.3 flask Collecting package metadata: done Solving environment: done ## Package Plan ## environment location: /home/tan/Workspace/tools/anaconda3/envs/myflask added / updated specs: - flask - python=3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Challenges: May 25, 2019</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/blog/30-day-challenges-2019-may-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:05:18 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/blog/30-day-challenges-2019-may-june/</guid>
      <description>I have taken a challenge whereid I will learn a new technology every day and blog it on this page for a month. The challenge started on May 25, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Is Not Our Enemy</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/goodreads/man-is-not-our-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 22:19:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/goodreads/man-is-not-our-enemy/</guid>
      <description>The original post is located at plumvillage.org.
A poem by Thich Nhat Hanh Promise me,
promise me this day,
promise me now,
while the sun is overhead
exactly at the zenith,
promise me:
Even as they
strike you down
with a mountain of hatred and violence;
even as they step on you and crush you
like a worm,
even as they dismember and disembowel you,
remember brother, remember:
man is not our enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/me/hire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 17:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/me/hire/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a remote full time job as Java Backend Engineer.
You can view my CV online here.
Drop me email via honhattan90@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CV</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/me/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 17:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/me/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education  2008 - 2012 BSc, Information Technology; University of Natural Sciences, HCMC  Minor: Software Engineering   Professional Summary  Hands on more than 7 years&amp;rsquo;s of experience in java programming language and its related technologies like java ee, spring framework, restful web services. Have strong background in programming, software analysis and design. Have experience on different software domains like mobile payment, uberization, e-commerce. Critical thinking, have ability to think different solutions and produce code with a good quality and maintainable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>