<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tan Ho</title>
    <link>http://honhattan.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tan Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:09:41 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://honhattan.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Three - Learning Go</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-three-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:09:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-three-golang/</guid>
      <description>This is the day three of 30-Day Challenges in learning new technoloy everyday.
The title for today is Learning Go. To be honest I tried to write some line of codes in Go before but my understanding about the language is discreted. So I hope after this day, I will achieve my studing goal in a more systematic way!
A brief history about Go. Go is statically typed, complied programming language designed at Google by Robert Griesemer (V8 engine, Java Hotspt VM), Rob Pike (Unix Team, UTF-8) and Ken Tompson (Unix).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Two - Java Daemon Thread</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-two-java-thread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 17:51:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-two-java-thread/</guid>
      <description>A daemon thread is a thread that is considered doing some tasks in the background like handling requests or various chronjobs that can exits in an application.
Properties  It can not prevent JVM from exiting when all user threads finish their executions. It is an utmost low priority thread.  Methods  public final void setDaemon(boolean on): This method is used to mark the current thread as daemon thread or normal thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One - Flask Framework</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-one-flask-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 20:08:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/challenges/day-one-flask-framework/</guid>
      <description>Create a new environment for our example.
conda create -n myflask python=3.7.3 flask We create an envionment with flask package and specified python version 3.7.3. If version is not specified, newest version is downloaded.
Below is what the output will look like on my terminal.
(base) tan@tan-pc:~/Workspace/py/my-flask-app$ conda create -n myflask python=3.7.3 flask Collecting package metadata: done Solving environment: done ## Package Plan ## environment location: /home/tan/Workspace/tools/anaconda3/envs/myflask added / updated specs: - flask - python=3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Challenges: May 25, 2019</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/challenges/30-day-challenges-2019-may-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:05:18 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/challenges/30-day-challenges-2019-may-june/</guid>
      <description>I have taken a challenge whereid I will learn a new technology every day and blog it on this page for a month. The challenge started on May 25, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Is Not Our Enemy</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/goodreads/man-is-not-our-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 22:19:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/goodreads/man-is-not-our-enemy/</guid>
      <description>The original post is located at plumvillage.org.
A poem by Thich Nhat Hanh Promise me,
promise me this day,
promise me now,
while the sun is overhead
exactly at the zenith,
promise me:
Even as they
strike you down
with a mountain of hatred and violence;
even as they step on you and crush you
like a worm,
even as they dismember and disembowel you,
remember brother, remember:
man is not our enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 17:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/me/about/</guid>
      <description>A developer with experience in building intelligent &amp;amp; scalable applications using Java/JavaEE/Spring, Python.
Mobile development learner: building an application with flutter. Python learner
Hire me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/me/hire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 17:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/me/hire/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a remote full time job as Java Backend Engineer.
You can view my CV online here.
Drop me email via honhattan90@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CV</title>
      <link>http://honhattan.net/me/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 17:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://honhattan.net/me/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education  2008 - 2012 BSc, Information Technology; University of Natural Sciences, HCMC  Minor: Software Engineering   Professional Summary  Hands on more than 7 years&amp;rsquo;s of experience in java programming language and its related technologies like java ee, spring framework, restful web services. Have strong background in programming, software analysis and design. Have experience on different software domains like mobile payment, uberization, e-commerce. Critical thinking, have ability to think different solutions and produce code with a good quality and maintainable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>